Philip M. Sheppard Papers 1911-1976 1940-1976 Mss.Ms.Coll.65
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1946-1983; 28 boxes, 14 lin. feet
  - Duryee, Samuel S., Jr., 1962 (Box Series I-8)
  - Dyer, K.F., 1972-74 (Box Series I-8)
  - Dyson-Hudson, V. Rada, 1953; 1970 (Box Series I-8)
  - EP Group of Companies, n.d. (Box Series I-8)
  - EST (Edizioni Scientifiche e Techniche), 1967-68 (Box Series I-8)
  - Easton, Michael D.L., 1969-75 (Box Series I-8)
  - Easton, Nigel T., 1961 (Box Series I-8)
  - Eaton, [?] (Mrs.), 1975 (Box Series I-8)
  - Ecology, 1961 (Box Series I-8)
  - Edgeloe, V.A., 1962 (Box Series I-8)
  - Edmunds, Malcolm, 1967 (Box Series I-8)
  - Edward, J.R., n.d. (Box Series I-8)
  - Edwards, E.E., 1957 (Box Series I-8)
  - Edwards, F. Ronald, 1967 (Box Series I-8)
  - Edwards, G.W. Ant[h?]ony, 1955 (Box Series I-8)
  - Edwards, John H., 1965-74 (Box Series I-8)
  - Edwards, Ken[neth] J.R., 1973 (Box Series I-8)
  - Edwards, Roy L., 1953; 1955 (Box Series I-8)
  - Eff, Donald, 1957-58 (Box Series I-8)
  - Ehrlich, I., n.d. (Box Series I-8)
  - Ehrlich, Paul R., 1957-72 (Box Series I-8)
  - Elgood, J.H., 1962 (Box Series I-8)
    -See also Ser.I, Angseesing, Joseph P.A.
  - Eliot, J. (Box Series I-8)
  - Ellams, D.L., 1968 (Box Series I-8)
  - Elsevier Excerpta Medica North-Holland, 1975 (Box Series I-8)
  - Elson, C.J., 1970-72 (Box Series I-8)
  - Elton, Arthur, 1958 (Box Series I-8)
  - Elton, CHarles, 1953-54 (Box Series I-8)
  - Emmel, Thomas C., 1968 (Box Series I-8)
  - Emmett, H.E.G., 1959 (Box Series I-8)
  - Emsley, Julie C. (Box Series I-8)
    -See Ser.I, Emsley, Michael G.
  - Emsley, Michael G., 1963-70 (Box Series I-8)
    Emsley, Julie C.
    Ramlal, Sonny
    -See also Ser.I, Turner, John R.G. (1963)
  - Emslie, R.D. (Box Series I-8)
  - Ethiopian and African Drought Appeal (Box Series I-8)
  - Eugenics Review, 1960-[67] (Box Series I-8)
  - Eugenics Society, 1959-60; 1969 (Box Series I-8)
    Bertram, G.C.L.
  - Evans, D.R., 1975-76 (Box Series I-8)
  - Evans, Victoria H., 1969-72 (Box Series I-8)
  - Evolution, 1960-1962; 1972-1976 (Box Series I-8)
    Lerner, I. Michael
    Evolution; Genetics -- Butterflies, moths; Genetics -- Snails; Lerner, Isadore Michael; Publication -- Evolution; Referee's report
  - Ewbank, Roger, 1962 (Box Series I-8)
  - Ewer, T.K., 1975 (Box Series I-8)
  - Ewers, William Hector, 1966 (Box Series I-8)
  - F.A.S. (Federation of American Scientists), 1976 (Box Series I-9)
  - Fairey Air Surveys Ltd., 1961 (Box Series I-9)
  - Fairfax Bell, [?], 1957-58 (Box Series I-9)
  - Fairman, H.W., 1958 (Box Series I-9)
  - Falconer, Douglas S., 1958; 1969-73 (Box Series I-9)
    -See also Ser.I, Drummond, David C.
  - Falek, Arthur, 1952 (Box Series I-9)
  - Fanoni, Don, 1975 (Box Series I-9)
  - Farrell, James, 1964 (Box Series I-9)
  - Faulkner, Barry M., 1971; n.d. (Box Series I-9)
  - Fenlaugh, Patricia, 1968 (Box Series I-9)
  - Fenn, [?] (Sister), 1973 (Box Series I-9)
  - Ferguson, Douglas C., 1953 (Box Series I-9)
  - Ferguson, E.A. (Box Series I-9)
    -See Ser.I, Mayr, Ernst
  - Ferguson-Smith, M.A., 1976 (Box Series I-9)
    -See also Ser.I, Genetical Society
  - Fernández, Santiago I., 1972 (Box Series I-9)
  - Fernando, C.H., 1961 (Box Series I-9)
  - Fincham, John R.S., 1966-76 (Box Series I-9)
  - Finn, Ronald (Box Series I-9)
  - Finney, David J., 1954-70 (Box Series I-9)
    -See also Ser.III, Panaxia dominula (1953) - Oversize
  - Fischer, Mischa, 1953 (Box Series I-9)
  - Fisher, Ronald Aylmer (Sir), 1946-1961; 2 folders (Box Series I-9)
    -See also Ser.I, Runcorn, S.K.
    -See also Ser.II, Blood Groups and Natural Selection (1958)
    Cancer, chemotherapy; Conferences and symposia -- Darwin Centennial; Congratulations, greetings, thanks; Dobzhansky, Theodosius; Evolution; Fellowships, assistantships; Ford, Edmund Brisco; Genetics -- Butterflies, moths; Genetics -- Snails; Genetics of plants; Graduate study; Human genetics -- Blood groups; International Congress of Zoology; Laboratory techniques, equipment; Lectures, public speaking; Population genetics; Publication; Statistics, biostatistics, biometrics
    - Folder 1, 1946-1952 (Box Series I-9)
    - Folder 2, 1953-1961 (Box Series I-9)
  - Fitzpatrick, R.J., 1969 (Box Series I-9)
  - Flack, E.R., 1959 (Box Series I-9)
  - Fletcher, Brian H., 1966 (Box Series I-9)
  - Fogden, Michael P.L., 1964-65 (Box Series I-9)
  - Fones, C.C. (Mrs.), 1969 (Box Series I-9)
  - Fones, David M., 1966; 1969 (Box Series I-9)
  - Ford, Charles E., 1958; 1966-70 (Box Series I-9)
    -See also Ser.I, Clarke Cyril A.
    -See also Ser.I, Ford, E.B. (1967)
  - Ford, Edmund Brisco, 1949-1976; 16 folders (Box Series I-9)
    Clarke, Cyril A. (1963)
    Cook, Laurence [M.] (1961)
    Ford, C.E. (1967)
    -See also Ser.I, Britton, E.B.
    -See also Ser.I, Clarke, Cyril A. (1955)
    -See also Ser.I, Dobzhansky, Theodosius
    -See also Ser.I, Downham, David
    -See also Ser.I, Kettlewell, H.B.D. (1960)
    -See also Ser.I, Mariani, Mario
    -See also Ser.I, Mayr, Ernst
    -See also Ser.I, Rockefeller Foundation
    Biographical and personal data; Clarke, Cyril Astley; Conferences and symposia; Darlington, Cyril Dean; Dobzhansky, Theodosius; Drosophila genetics; Ecology; Educational matters; Evolution; Fellowships, assistantships; Fisher, Ronald Aylmer; Genetics -- Butterflies, moths; Genetics -- Wasps; Graduate study; Human genetics; Human genetics -- Blood groups; Lectures, public speaking; Medical research; Molecular genetics; Population genetics; Publication; Recommendations; Requests for reprints; Reviews; Society for the Study of Evolution; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements; Turner, John R. G.; Unpublished manuscripts, notes, etc.
    - Folder 1, 1949-1957 (Box Series I-9)
    - Folder 2, 1958 (Box Series I-9)
    - Folder 3, 1959-1960 (Box Series I-9)
    - Folder 4, 1961 (Box Series I-9)
    - Folder 5, 1962 (Box Series I-9)
    - Folder 6, 1963 (Box Series I-9)
    - Folder 7, 1964 (Box Series I-9)
    - Folder 8, 1965 (Box Series I-9)
    - Folder 9, 1966 (Box Series I-9)
    - Folder 10, 1967 (Box Series I-9)
    - Folder 11, 1968 (Box Series I-9)
    - Folder 12, 1969 (Box Series I-10)
    - Folder 13, 1970 (Box Series I-10)
    - Folder 14, 1971-1972 (Box Series I-10)
    - Folder 15, 1973-1974 (Box Series I-10)
    - Folder 16, 1975-1976 (Box Series I-10)
  - Ford, W. H., 1975-1976 (Box Series I-10)
  - Forrest, A. (Mrs. ), 1970 (Box Series I-10)
  - Foulds, Marie, 1968 (Box Series I-10)
  - Francis, E. H., 1969 (Box Series I-10)
  - Frank, J. Howard, 1975 (Box Series I-10)
  - Fraser Roberts, John A., 1955-1957 (Box Series I-10)
    - See also Ser. I. Clarke, Cyril A.
  - Frazer, J. F. D., 1954 (Box Series I-10)
  - Frazzette, Thomas H., 1962 (Box Series I-10)
  - Fredga, Karl, 1976 (Box Series I-10)
  - Freeman, Charles B., 1975 (Box Series I-10)
  - Freeman, Paul, 1960-1964 (Box Series I-10)
    Mattingly, Peter F.
  - Freeman and Co., Ltd., 1960, 1972-1975 (Box Series I-10)
  - French, Eric, 1967 (Box Series I-10)
  - Freshwater Biological Association, 1974 (Box Series I-10)
  - Friedhoff, Arnold J. (Box Series I-10)
    - See Ser. I. Clarke, Cyril A.
  - Fröhlich. H., 1973 (Box Series I-10)
  - Frota-Pessoa, O., 1965, 1971 (Box Series I-10)
  - Fryer, R. A., 1970 (Box Series I-10)
  - Fukatami, Akishi, 1968-1969 (Box Series I-10)
  - Fundaçao-Prêmio André Dreyfus, 1953-1954 (Box Series I-10)
  - Fur and Feather, 1953 (Box Series I-10)
  - Gain, Louie A., 1952 (Box Series I-10)
  - Gait, N. H., 1956 (Box Series I-10)
    - See also Sr. I. Morris, Desmond
  - Ganaj, William, 1961 (Box Series I-10)
  - Gardiner, A. A. M., 1954 (Box Series I-10)
  - Gardiner, Brian O. C., 1957, 1974 (Box Series I-10)
  - Gaskell, T. J., 1966, 1968 (Box Series I-10)
  - Gedda, Luigi, 1959 (Box Series I-10)
  - Gelder, Stuart R., 1967 (Box Series I-10)
  - Genetical Society (Box Series I-10)
    Ferguson-Smith, M. A.
    Fincham, John R. S.
    Lewis, Daniel
    Riley, Ralph
    Roper, J. Allan
    Subak-Sharpe, John H.
  - Genetics, 1953-1970 (Box Series I-10)
  - George, David R., 1968-1976 (Box Series I-10)
  - George Allen & Unwin, Ltd., 1952-58, 1972-73 (Box Series I-10)
  - Georghiou, G. P., 1969 (Box Series I-10)
  - Gérard, Francis, 1968 (Box Series I-10)
  - Gerrard, D. A., 1973 (Box Series I-10)
  - Gibbs, H. L., 1956 (Box Series I-11)
  - Gibson, C. W. D., 1973 (Box Series I-11)
  - Gilbert, Larry E., 1966-1973 (Box Series I-11)
  - Gilbert, R. I., 1973-1976 (Box Series I-11)
  - Gill, Alison, 1962-1971 (Box Series I-11)
  - Gilham, Nicholas W., 1955 (Box Series I-11)
  - Gilmour, Douglas G., 1954, 1958 (Box Series I-11)
  - Glass, H. Bentley (Box Series I-11)
    - See Ser. I. Brower, Lincoln P.
  - Glenn, Stanley, 1961 (Box Series I-11)
  - Gliddon, C. J., 1972 (Box Series I-11)
  - Glover, Stuart W., 1972-1973 (Box Series I-11)
  - Glover, Tim D., 1973, 1975 (Box Series I-11)
  - Glynn, L. E. (Box Series I-11)
  - Gnome Photographic Products Ltd., 1968 (Box Series I-11)
  - Gobey, R. S., 1956 (Box Series I-11)
  - Godfrey, John (Box Series I-11)
    - Ser. Ser. I. Nuffield Foundation
  - Goodhart, Charles B., 1952-1975 (Box Series I-11)
  - Goodman, T. J., 1973 (Box Series I-11)
  - Goodson, Leslie (Box Series I-11)
    - Ser. Ser. I. Kettlewell, H. B. D. (1960)
  - Goodwin, H. B., 1968 (Box Series I-11)
  - Goodwin, Trevor W., 1972, 1975 (Box Series I-11)
  - Goose, D. H., 1965-1969 (Box Series I-11)
  - Gordon, ?, 1953 (Box Series I-11)
  - Gorer, P., 1956 (Box Series I-11)
  - Goswami, H. K., 1964 (Box Series I-11)
  - Gouthwaite, E. G., 1965 (Box Series I-11)
  - Govindras, Kulkarni Prakash, 1966 (Box Series I-11)
  - Gowers, Stuart, 1965-1972 (Box Series I-11)
  - Grab, B., 1968 (Box Series I-11)
    - See also Ser. I. Gratz, Norman G.
    - See also Ser. I. Macdonald, W. W.
    - See also Ser. I. Wright, J. W.
  - Graham, M. W. R., 1958 (Box Series I-11)
  - Graham, Peter, 1976 (Box Series I-11)
  - Granada TV, 1962-1969 (Box Series I-11)
  - Gratz, Norman G., 1966-1972 (Box Series I-11)
    Grab, B. (1967-1968)
  - Gray, G. (Mrs. ), 1971 (Box Series I-11)
  - Gray, P., 1960 (Box Series I-11)
  - Gray, T. R. G., 1965 (Box Series I-11)
  - Gray, W. J., 1957 (Box Series I-11)
  - Greaves, J. H., 1966-1971 (Box Series I-11)
  - Green, A. A., 1953 (Box Series I-11)
  - Green, E. A. (Mrs. ), 1972 (Box Series I-11)
  - Green, George, 1967 (Box Series I-11)
  - Green, L. L., 1976 (Box Series I-11)
  - Green, Wyman R., 1960 (Box Series I-11)
  - Greenwood, Jeremy John Denis, 1966-1974 (Box Series I-11)
  - Greenwood, S., 1973 (Box Series I-11)
  - Gregory, ?, 1956 (Box Series I-11)
  - Gregory, R. A., 1967 (Box Series I-11)
  - Griffin, Donald R., 1965 (Box Series I-11)
  - Griveaud, P. (Box Series I-11)
    - Ser. Ser. I. Vieu, R.
  - Groupair, 1973 (Box Series I-11)
  - Grüneberg, H., 1971-1972 (Box Series I-11)
  - Gubbay, A. D., 1955 (Box Series I-11)
  - Gunaratne, V. T. H. (Box Series I-11)
    - Ser. Ser. I. Clarke, Cyril A.
  - Gunn, D. L., 1965 (Box Series I-11)
  - Gurdon, John B., 1970-1971 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hagen, Don W., 1966-1972 (Box Series I-11)
  - Haldane, J. B. S. (John Burdon Sanderson), 1959, n.d.; 2.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-11)
    Clarke, Cyril Astley; Human genetics -- Blood groups; Population genetics; Publication -- Genetics; Requests for reprints
  - Halkka, Olli, 1973 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hall, G. B., 1955 (Box Series I-11)
  - Halliday, Jack, 1952-1953 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hallows, Bryan J., 1970-1976 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hamilton, W. D., 1971 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hancock, Bob, 1973 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hane, D., 1954 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hanley, W. B., 1962 (Box Series I-11)
  - Har, Tan Lay, 1966 (Box Series I-11)
  - Harbottle, Charles, 1976 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hardstaff, M., 1971 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hardy, Alister C., 1956-1965 (Box Series I-11)
    - See also Ser. I. Burkhardt, Valentino
  - Hardy, Barbara, 1975 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hardy, Michael, n.d. (Box Series I-11)
  - Hargreaves, Armitage, 1951-1965 (Box Series I-11)
  - Harmsworth, Desmond, 1951, 1954 (Box Series I-11)
  - Harper, John L. (Box Series I-11)
    MacFarlane, W.
  - Harper, Peter, 1964-1969 (Box Series I-11)
  - Harris, E. A. M., 1973 (Box Series I-11)
  - Harris, Henry, 1968-1970 (Box Series I-11)
  - Harris, R., 1969 (Box Series I-11)
  - Harris, Raymond C., 1968 (Box Series I-11)
  - Harrison, Geoffrey Ainsworth, 1964-1975 (Box Series I-11)
  - Harrison Matthews, L., 1960 (Box Series I-11)
    - See also Ser. I. Kettlewell, H. B. D. (1960)
  - Hart, M. G. R., 1969 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hartles, R. L., 1975 (Box Series I-11)
  - Harvey, Paul, 1970, 1974 (Box Series I-11)
    - See also Ser. I. Cain, Arthur (1971)
  - Harvey, R. J., 1955-1956 (Box Series I-11)
  - Haskell, Elsie, n.d. (Box Series I-11)
  - Haskell, Gordon, 1966-1967 (Box Series I-11)
  - Haskins, Caryl P., 1954, 1964-1966 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hawe, Philip, 1963 (Box Series I-11)
    Adamson, A. C.
  - Haworth, Geoffrey H., 1965, 1975 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hayes, William, 1960, 1972-1974 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hayman, D. L., 1967 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hayward, Chris, 1976 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hearnshaw, L. S., 1956 (Box Series I-12)
  - Heath, C., 1972 (Box Series I-12)
  - Heath, Sylvia M., 1966 (Box Series I-12)
  - Heathcote, Oliver, 1959 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hecht, Max K., 1968-1974, n.d. (Box Series I-12)
  - Heddle, D., 1955 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hedrick, Philip W., 1970 (Box Series I-12)
  - Heed, William, 1964 (Box Series I-12)
  - Heets, Edwain (Box Series I-12)
    - See Ser. I. Barton, Derek
  - Heineken Stichtung, 1976 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hemmings, R., 1967-1968 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hensman, Bertha, 1969-1970 (Box Series I-12)
  - Henson, H., 1967? (Box Series I-12)
  - Heredity, 1959, 1968-1970 (Box Series I-12)
    Thoday, John M.
    - See also Ser. I. Fincham, John R. S.
  - Herxheimer, Andrew, 1963 (Box Series I-12)
  - Heuch, Ivar, 1972-1973 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hewer, H. R., 1958 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hewitt, Godfrey, 1972-1974 (Box Series I-12)
  - Heywood, V. H., 1966-1972, n.d. (Box Series I-12)
  - Hibbard, B. M., 1971 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hickson, R. G., 1972-1976 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hinde, Robert A., 1974 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hinton, H. E., 1968 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hobday, ?, 1976 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hobhouse, John R., 1957 (Box Series I-12)
    - See also Ser. III. Research notebook #1 (1911)
  - Hobson, Derek, 1968 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hobsons Press, 1976 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hocking, K. S., 1970 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hodgson, W. E., 1963 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hoffman, Klaus, 1955-1956 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hogg, M. E., 1971 (Box Series I-12)
  - Holker, J. S. E., 1968-1969 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hollander, William, 1969-1971 (Box Series I-12)
  - Holliday, Gilbert A., 1957 (Box Series I-12)
  - Holling, C. S., 1973 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hollingsworth, M., 1972 (Box Series I-12)
  - Holloway, Bruce, 1972 (Box Series I-12)
  - Holmes, R., 1953, 1972 (Box Series I-12)
  - Holmes, William, 1963 (Box Series I-12)
  - Holroyd, R. B., 1954 (Box Series I-12)
  - Holt, Elizabeth, 1974 (Box Series I-12)
  - Holway, Peter H., 1971 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hope, Rory M., 1971 (Box Series I-12)
  - Horejí, J., 1966 (Box Series I-12)
  - Horner, Ken, 1974-1976 (Box Series I-12)
    Parsons, Peter A.
  - Horovitz, A., 1969 (Box Series I-12)
  - Horridge, G. Adrian, 1971 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hossain, M. Altaf, 1961-1966 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hotel Continental, 1972 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hotel de Zalm, 1963 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hotel Excelsior, 1972 (Box Series I-12)
  - Houghton, James Anthony, 1966-1969 (Box Series I-12)
  - Houghton, Mifflin Co., 1973-1974 (Box Series I-12)
  - Houyez, P., 1952 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hovanitz, William, 1952-53, 1973-74 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hovell, G. J. R., 1963 (Box Series I-12)
  - Howarth, T. G., 1958-1973 (Box Series I-12)
  - Howel Evans, William, 1963 (Box Series I-12)
  - Howell, ?, 1960 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hsu, Andrew, 1961 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hsu, Sze-Jih, 1961 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hu, Stephen M. K., 1961 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hudson, R. C. L., 1961 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hughes, D. L., 1958 (Box Series I-12)
    - See also Ser. I. Kay, Robert S.
  - Hughes Jones, N. C. (Box Series I-12)
  - Huheey, James E., 1960-1975 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hull, Peter, 1968-1969 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hulls, Wendy, 1965-1966 (Box Series I-12)
  - Humphreys, Arthur R., 1971 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hunt, James P., 1968-1970 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hunter, Clare, 1976 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hurry, Stephen, 1970 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hutchings, ?, 1964 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hutchinson, G. E., 1955 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hutchinson, T. C., 1960 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hutchinson Publishing Group (Box Series I-12)
    - Folder #1, 1956-1959 (Box Series I-12)
    - Folder #2, 1960-1967 (Box Series I-12)
    - Folder #3, 1968-1973 (Box Series I-12)
    - Folder #4, 1974-1976 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hutt, F. B., 1960 (Box Series I-12)
  - Huxley, Julian S., 1958; 2.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-12)
    - See also Ser. I. Kettlewell, H. B. D. (1963)
    Research support
  - Hyland, G. J., 1975 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hynes, D. L., 1958 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hynes, H. B. Noel, 1962-1964 (Box Series I-12)
  - Illsley, Irene R., 1973 (Box Series I-13)
  - Impulse, 1961-1962 (Box Series I-13)
  - Independent University. Planning Board, 1969 (Box Series I-13)
  - Ingram, Vernon M., 1974 (Box Series I-13)
  - Institute of Biology, 1966-1975 (Box Series I-13)
  - International Congress of Cybernetics, 1969 (Box Series I-13)
  - International Union of Biochemistry, 1976 (Box Series I-13)
  - Irwin, M. R., 1955-1956 (Box Series I-13)
  - Irwin, V., 1955 (Box Series I-13)
  - Isbill, Max, 1952 (Box Series I-13)
  - Ishizaki, Hironori, 1962 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jackson, T. H. B., 1956-1957 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jagoe, Alan, 1972-1973 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jamieson, Alan, 1969 (Box Series I-13)
  - JANIS (Journalists' Auxiliary News Information Service), 1973 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jao, Lien-Tsair, 1961-1962 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jayakuru, ?, 1973 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jeffery, F. W., 1953-1954 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jeffery, Paul, 1952 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jelnes, Jesn Erik, 1973 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jenkins, Pat, 1976 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jerome, S. A., 1966 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jewkes, John, 1968-1969 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jinks, John L., 1965-1976 (Box Series I-13)
  - John, Bernard, 1968 (Box Series I-13)
  - John Innes Horticultural Institution, 1956 (Box Series I-13)
  - Johnson, Clifford, 1959, 1965 (Box Series I-13)
  - Johnson, D. J. E., 1970 (Box Series I-13)
  - Johnson, F., 1951 (Box Series I-13)
  - Johnson, George B., 1971 (Box Series I-13)
    Dobzhansky, Thoedosius
    Powell, Jeffrey
  - Johnson, J. H., 1962 (Box Series I-13)
    Cook, Laurence M.
    -See also Ser. I. Clarke, Cyril A.
  - Johnston, Peter, 1968 (Box Series I-13)
  - Johnstone, John, 1951 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jones, Mrs., 1975 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jones, A. L., 1969-1970 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jones, E. J., 1955 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jones, J. S., 1971-1972 (Box Series I-13)
    - See also Ser. I. Cain, Arthur J.
  - Jones, J. W., 1956-1966, 1974 (Box Series I-13)
    Christopher, R.
    Journal of Fish Biology
    Whitaker, R. J.
  - Jones, Margaret A., 1964 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jones, Pamela, 1968-1969 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jones, Rosemary O., 1970 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jones, W. R., 1967 (Box Series I-13)
  - Journal of Animal Ecology, 1967-1975 (Box Series I-13)
    Broadhead, Edward
    Southern, H. N.
    - See also Ser. I. Macdonald W. W.
  - Journal of Comparative Pathology and Therapeutics, 1962 (Box Series I-13)
    White, Edwin G.
  - Journal of Fish Biology, 1974-1975 (Box Series I-13)
    - See also Ser. I. Jones, J. W.
  - Journal of Medical Genetics, 1972-1974 (Box Series I-13)
  - Journal of Research on the Lepidoptera (Box Series I-13)
    - See Ser. I. Hovanitz, William
  - Journal of Zoology, 1960-1972 (Box Series I-13)
  - Judd, Burke H., 1967 (Box Series I-13)
  - Judd, W. W., 1953 (Box Series I-13)
  - Juva, Mikko, 1973 (Box Series I-13)
  - Kadarsan, Sampurno, 1961-1962 (Box Series I-13)
  - Kalmus, H., 1953-1958 (Box Series I-13)
  - Karlin, Samuel, 1974 (Box Series I-13)
    Nevo, Eviator
  - Karunaratne, P. B. (Box Series I-13)
  - Kay, Andrew M. (Box Series I-13)
  - Kay, Quentin, 1970 (Box Series I-13)
  - Kay, Robert S., 1966 (Box Series I-13)
    Hughes, D. L.
  - Kearney, E. M., 1963 (Box Series I-13)
  - Kearsey, M. J., 1967-1974, n.d. (Box Series I-13)
    Barnes, Brian W.
    - See also Ser. I. Barnes, Brian W.
  - Keenleyside, Miles H. A., 1954 (Box Series I-13)
  - Keep, A. P., 1967 (Box Series I-13)
  - Keir, H. M., 1972 (Box Series I-13)
  - Keith, J. L., 1965 (Box Series I-13)
  - Kellett, D. N. (Box Series I-13)
  - Kelly, Thomas, 1958-1975 (Box Series I-13)
  - Kemp, P. L., 1957-1960 (Box Series I-13)
  - Kendall, Michael, 1971 (Box Series I-13)
  - Kennedy, John S., 1961, 1971 (Box Series I-13)
  - Kerr, Warwick E., 1958, 1968-1972 (Box Series I-13)
  - Kershaw, Kenneth A., 1964 (Box Series I-13)
  - Kershaw, William E., 1967-1973 (Box Series I-13)
  - Kettlewell, H. B. D. (Henry Bernard Davis), 1952-1976; 5 folders (Box Series I-13)
    Barnes, ? (1952)
    Ford, E. B. (1960)
    Goodson, Leslie (1960)
    Harrison, Matthews L. (1960)
    Huxley, Julian S. (1963)
    - See also Ser. I. Newman, L. Hugh
    Biographical and personal data; Cain, Arthur James; Clarke, Cyril Astley; Conferences and symposia; Darlington, Cyril Dean; Darwin, Charles; Dobzhansky, Theodosius; Evolution; Ford, Edmund Brisco; Genetics -- Butterflies, moths; Haldane, John Burdon Sanderson; Huxley, Julian; International Congress of Genetics; Lectures, public speaking; Mendel, Gregor; Oxford University; Population genetics; Publication; Publication -- Evolution; Radiation genetics; Requests for reprints; Travel -- Brazil; Unpublished manuscripts, notes, etc.
    - Folder #1, 1952-1960 (Box Series I-13)
    - Folder #2, 1961-1962 (Box Series I-13)
    - Folder #3, 1963-1965 (Box Series I-13)
    - Folder #4, 1966-1967 (Box Series I-14)
    - Folder #5, 1968-1976 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kidd, Douglas J., 1968, 1974 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kidwell, James F., 1967-1968 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kimura, Motoo, 1955-1976; 51.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-14)
    Mary, Ernst
    - See also Ser. I. Dempster, Everett R.
    American Institute of Biological Sciences; Biographical and personal data; Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory; Conferences and symposia; Congratulations, greetings, thanks -- Darwin medal; Crow, James F.; Evolution; Fisher, Ronald Aylmer; Genetics -- Butterflies, moths; Genetics -- Snails; Genetics of plants; Honors -- Walden prize; Human genetics -- Blood groups; International Congress of Genetics -- Twelfth Congress; International Congress of Zoology; Invitations; Li, Ching Chun; Mayr, Ernst; Photographs; Population genetics; Publication; Requests for reprints; Statistics, biostatistics, biometrics; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements; Wright, Sewall
  - King, A. S., 1969-1970 (Box Series I-14)
  - King, F., 1963 (Box Series I-14)
  - King, J. O. L., 1957-1972 (Box Series I-14)
    - See also Ser. I. Werrett, W. F.
  - King, Michael, 1959 (Box Series I-14)
  - King, Peter, 1973 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kinlen, Leo (Box Series I-14)
  - Kinley, D. L., 1968 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kirby, ?, n.d. (Box Series I-14)
  - Kirby, David, 1966, 1968 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kirby, Michael A., 1971 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kitani, Yoshiaki, 1975 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kitchingman, Gilliam, 1974-1976 (Box Series I-14)
  - KLM (Royal Dutch Airlines), 1960 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kloss, Gertrude R., 1972 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kneale, Heather, 1968 (Box Series I-14)
  - Knox, E. G., 1960-1961 (Box Series I-14)